<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Write rules as code on OpenFisca</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/</link><description>Recent content in Write rules as code on OpenFisca</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://openfisca.org/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/about/</guid><description>Digital common OpenFisca is a digital common: it is free and open source software designed, developed and used by many people around the world through democratic, horizontal governance processes such as Requests For Comments (RFCs) and open discussions.
Community As contributors to a common, we collectively do our best to make our community a space where everyone can express themselves and feel free to be who they are. Our rules to that end are grown progressively as we learn what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item><item><title>Available packages</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/packages/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Legal notice</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/legal-notice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/legal-notice/</guid><description>Editor OpenFisca Association (association under French law loi 1901)
42 rue Rosenwald, 75015 Paris - France
contact@openfisca.org
Editorial director Matti Schneider
Hosting provider GitHub, Inc
88 Colin P Kelly Jr St
San Francisco, CA 94107 - United States
+1 (877) 448-4820</description></item><item><title>OpenFisca Association Rules of Procedure</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/rules-of-procedure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/association/rules-of-procedure/</guid><description>1. Working language Due to its international nature, the Foundation operates with English as its working language.
2. Membership 1) Eligibility A. College A (college of supporters) The only condition for joining college A is to pay the membership fee.
B. College B (college of legal entities using OpenFisca) Only legal entities (and not natural persons) can join college B. To join college B, a legal entity must:
pay the membership fee; list at least one active use case on the public OpenFisca website.</description></item><item><title>Page not found 😞</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/404/</guid><description>The page you tried to access could not be found.
If you typed the address manually, double-check it for typos. If you accessed this page through a bookmark, it might be outdated. If you reached this page through a link on this website, this is embarrassing —please let us know!
Back to homepage</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/privacy/</guid><description>Website When you visit this website, a small text file (a “cookie”) gets saved on your computer. This enables us to measure the number of visits and which pages are most read.
This website does not show a consent banner for cookies, why? Out tracking tool, Matomo, is set up in compliance with the &amp;ldquo;Cookies&amp;rdquo; recommandations from the French data privacy authority, the CNIL, which allows the lack of prior consent.</description></item><item><title>Showcase</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/showcase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/showcase/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Statutes of the OpenFisca Association</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/statutes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/association/statutes/</guid><description>Preamble OpenFisca is a digital commons enabling anyone to transform law and rules into computer code.
Created in 2011 with support from the French government1, OpenFisca has been adopted by a growing number of public and research actors, and subsequently by the private sector. OpenFisca has been progressively deployed in a growing number of regions around the world, and now covers every continent. It is the collaboration of a diverse ecosystem on a single technical object that has enabled this tool to make the innovations promised by the &amp;ldquo;Rules as Code&amp;rdquo; approach a reality.</description></item><item><title>Styleguide</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/styleguide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/styleguide/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>