<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Write rules as code on OpenFisca</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/</link><description>Recent content in Write rules as code on OpenFisca</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://openfisca.org/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/about/</guid><description>Digital common OpenFisca is a digital common: it is free and open source software designed, developed and used by many people around the world through democratic, horizontal governance processes such as Requests For Comments (RFCs) and open discussions.
Community As contributors to a common, we collectively do our best to make our community a space where everyone can express themselves and feel free to be who they are. Our rules to that end are grown progressively as we learn what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item><item><title>Available packages</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/packages/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Legal notice</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/legal-notice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/legal-notice/</guid><description>Editor Agence Nationale de la Cohésion des Territoires
https://agence-cohesion-territoires.gouv.fr/
Mission incubateur de services numériques
20, avenue de Ségur
TSA 10717
75 334 Paris Cedex 07
+33 1 85 58 60 00
Editorial director
Caroline Corbal
Hosting provider GitHub, Inc
88 Colin P Kelly Jr St
San Francisco, CA 94107 - United States
+1 (877) 448-4820
Accessibility This website has not yet been audited for compliance with digital accessibility standards. If you encounter an accessibility problem that prevents you from accessing a content or a functionality of the site, please let us know.</description></item><item><title>Page not found 😞</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/404/</guid><description>The page you tried to access could not be found.
If you typed the address manually, double-check it for typos. If you accessed this page through a bookmark, it might be outdated. If you reached this page through a link on this website, this is embarrassing —please let us know!
Back to homepage</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/tracking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/tracking/</guid><description>Website When you visit this website, a small text file (a “cookie”) gets saved on your computer. This enables us to measure the number of visits and which pages are most read.
This website does not show a consent banner for cookies, why? Out tracking tool, Matomo, is set up in compliance with the &amp;ldquo;Cookies&amp;rdquo; recommandations from the French data privacy authority, the CNIL, which allows the lack of prior consent.</description></item><item><title>Showcase</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/showcase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/showcase/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Styleguide</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/styleguide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/styleguide/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>