<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OpenFisca</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/</link><description>Recent content on OpenFisca</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://openfisca.org/en/association/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/working-groups/technical/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/association/working-groups/technical/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="technical-working-group">Technical working group&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="motivation">Motivation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The Technical Working Group is a space for technical contributors to meet, exchange and share their experiences, tools and products developed with Openfisca. It is a place to discuss the limitations of Openfisca, the problems encountered, and the improvements that could be made to the software.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The aim of these meetings is to expose technical contributors working on openfisca to the work and thoughts of other members of the community, to showcase tools or products developed by members of the community, and to share feedback on developments made with openfisca with a view to improving it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OpenFisca Association Rules of Procedure</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/rules-of-procedure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/association/rules-of-procedure/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="1-working-language">1. Working language&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Due to its international nature, the Foundation operates with English as its working language.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="2-membership">2. Membership&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="1-eligibility">1) Eligibility&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="a-college-a-college-of-supporters">A. College A (college of supporters)&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>The only condition for joining college A is to pay the membership fee.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="b-college-b-college-of-legal-entities-using-openfisca">B. College B (college of legal entities using OpenFisca)&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Only legal entities (and not natural persons) can join college B. To join college B, a legal entity must:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>pay the membership fee;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>list at least one active use case on the public OpenFisca website.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="c-college-c-college-of-legal-entities-selling-openfisca-implementation-support-services">C. College C (college of legal entities selling OpenFisca implementation support services)&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Only legal entities (and not natural persons) can join college C. To join college C, a legal entity must:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Statutes of the OpenFisca Association</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/statutes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/association/statutes/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="preamble">Preamble&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>OpenFisca is a digital commons enabling anyone to transform law and rules into computer code.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Created in 2011 with support from the French government&lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>, OpenFisca has been adopted by a growing number of public and research actors, and subsequently by the private sector. OpenFisca has been progressively deployed in a growing number of regions around the world, and now covers every continent. It is the collaboration of a diverse ecosystem on a single technical object that has enabled this tool to make the innovations promised by the &amp;ldquo;Rules as Code&amp;rdquo; approach a reality.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>