<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OpenFisca</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/</link><description>Recent content on OpenFisca</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://openfisca.org/en/association/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OpenFisca Association Rules of Procedure</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/rules-of-procedure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/association/rules-of-procedure/</guid><description>1. Working language Due to its international nature, the Foundation operates with English as its working language.
2. Membership 1) Eligibility A. College A (college of supporters) The only condition for joining college A is to pay the membership fee.
B. College B (college of legal entities using OpenFisca) Only legal entities (and not natural persons) can join college B. To join college B, a legal entity must:
pay the membership fee; list at least one active use case on the public OpenFisca website.</description></item><item><title>Statutes of the OpenFisca Association</title><link>https://openfisca.org/en/association/statutes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://openfisca.org/en/association/statutes/</guid><description>Preamble OpenFisca is a digital commons enabling anyone to transform law and rules into computer code.
Created in 2011 with support from the French government1, OpenFisca has been adopted by a growing number of public and research actors, and subsequently by the private sector. OpenFisca has been progressively deployed in a growing number of regions around the world, and now covers every continent. It is the collaboration of a diverse ecosystem on a single technical object that has enabled this tool to make the innovations promised by the &amp;ldquo;Rules as Code&amp;rdquo; approach a reality.</description></item></channel></rss>